Finding Aid for Vice President for Student Affairs (University of Michigan) Records
Bentley Historical Library
- James A. Lewis, Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1908-1964; 1954-1964
  - Student Organizations (Historical File), 1908-1965
    - Committee for Displaced Students, 1948-1952 (Box 4)
    - Committee to End Discrimination, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - Congress (Independent Men), 1939-1946 (Box 4)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, 1926-1930 (Box 4)
    - Council for Academic Freedom, 1947-1948 (Box 4)
    - Council for International Living, 1949-1958 (Box 4)
    - Delta Zeta, 1922-1948 (Box 4)
    - Democracy in Education Conference, 1950 (Box 4)
    - Evangelical Students, 1931 (Box 4)
    - Freshman Luncheon Club, 1932-1937 (Box 4)
    - Friars, 1944 (Box 4)
    - Frosh-Soph. Weekend, 1949-1950 (Box 4)
    - Gargoyle, 1947-1965 (Box 4)
    - Gothic Film Society, 1949-1964 (Box 4)
    - Inner Gate, 1922 (Box 4)
    - Inter-Arts Union, 1949-1955 (Box 4)
    - Intercooperative Council, 1942-1959 (Box 4)
    - Interfraternity Council, 1936-1958 (Box 5)
    - Interfraternity Council Ball, 1940-1954 (Box 5)
    - International Ball, 1942-1959 (Box 5)
    - International Center, 1942 (Box 5)
    - International Relations Club, 1932-1952 (Box 5)
    - International Week, 1957-1960 (Box 5)
    - Interracial Association, 1942-1948 (Box 5)
    - Inter-Sorority Association, 1922-1927 (Box 5)
    - J-Hop, 1913-1961; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Junior Panhellenic Council, 1949-1958 (Box 5)
    - Karl Marx Society, 1940-1947 (Box 5)
    - Landscape Club, 1926-1932 (Box 5)
    - Men's Glee Club, 1949-1955 (Box 5)
    - Men's Judiciary Council, 1940-1953 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Education Club, 1949-1957 (Box 5)
    - Michigan League, 1949-1961 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Post War Council, 1942-1945 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Sailing Club, 1948-1957 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Union, 1947-1955 (Box 5)
    - Michigan Youth for Democratic Action, 1944-1947; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Mimes, 1930-1957 (Box 5)
    - Movie Makers, 1938 (Box 5)
    - NAACP, 1951-1960 (Box 5)
    - National Student Association, 1949-1956 (Box 5)
    - National Student Forum, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
    - National Student League, 1923-1935 (Box 5)
    - Philippines (University of), 1945-1961 (Box 5)
    - Political Issues Club, 1956-1961 (Box 5)
    - Publicity, Promotion, Solicitations, 1951-1955 (Box 5)
    - Round Up Club, 1922 (Box 5)
    - Russian Relief, 1942 (Box 5)
    - Scimitar, 1938-1948 (Box 5)
    - Slide Rule Ball, 1948-1956 (Box 5)
    - Society for Peaceful Alternatives, 1951-1954 (Box 5)
    - Society of Women Engineers, 1941-1960 (Box 5)
    - South Africa Union, 1916 (Box 5)
    - Student Advisory Committee, 1922-1923 (Box 5)
    - Student Book Exchange, 1939-1947 (Box 5)
    - Student Christian Association, 1922 (Box 5)
    - Student Council, 1925-1939 (Box 5)
    - Student Undergraduate Council, 1922-1935 (Box 5)
    - Student League for Industrial Democracy, 1935-1947 (Box 5)
    - Student Legislature, 1946-1954 (Box 5)
    - Student Religious Association, 1937-1956 (Box 5)
    - Student Volunteer Band for Foreign Missions, 1910 (Box 5)
    - Student Workers Association, 1936 (Box 5)
    - Swingout, 1928-1946 (Box 5)
    - Toastmasters Club, 1934-1941 (Box 5)
    - Tug Week, 1932-1949 (Box 5)
    - Union Opera, 1929-1956 (Box 5)
    - Young Progressives of Michigan, 1946-1952; 2 folders (Box 5)
  - Topical Files
    - Bureau of School Services: Executive Committee, 1958-1962 (Box 6)
    - Civil Defense, 1961-1962 (Box 6)
    - Fraternities, 1953-1957
      - Advisors Association, 1955-1956 (Box 6)
      - Fraternity Row on North Campus, 1955-1957 (Box 6)
      - Housing, Health, and Safety, 1956-1957 (Box 6)
      - President's Assembly, 1956-1957 (Box 6)
      - Services Committee, 1953-1957 (Box 6)
    - Freshman Admission Materials, 1963-1964 (Box 6)
    - Housing, Summer 1955-1956 (Box 6)
    - Human Relations Board, 1958-1963 (Box 6)
    - Interfraternity Council, 1924-1961; 1954-1958
      - General, 1954-1957 (Box 6)
      - Judiciary, 1955 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Workshop, 1957-1959 (Box 6)
      - National Conference, 1954-1958; 5 folders (Box 6)
    - Interfraternity Council 1924-1961 1954-1958 (cont.)
      - Scholarship, 1924-1961 (Box 6)
      - Treasurer, 1953-1959 (Box 6)
    - Interfraternity Research and Advisory Council, 1954-1958 (Box 6)
    - International Center, 1955-1962 (Box 6)
    - Junior Interfraternity Council, 1950-1958; 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Lecture Committee Study, 1956-1961 (Box 6)
    - Michigan Union: Student-Faculty-Administration Conference, 1955 (Box 6)
    - Scholarships, 1956-1964 (Box 6)
    - Student Affairs, 1953-1964
      - Committee on Student Housing, 1955-1956 (Box 6)
      - Michigan League, 1962-1963 (Box 6)
      - Michigan Union, 1953-1964; 3 folders (Box 6)
      - Newcomb Study, 1959-1961 (Box 6)
      - Student Activities Building, 1954-1960 (Box 6)
      - Student Government Council, 1955-1960 (Box 6)
      - Student Governor's Conference, 1960-1962 (Box 6)
      - Student Loans, 1954-1964 (Box 6)
      - Walter, Eric A., Correspondence, 1957-1964 (Box 6)
      - Zerman, Bill, Memoranda to Dean Rea, 1954-1955 (Box 6)
- Richard L. Cutler, Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1950-1969; 1964-1968
  In the mid-1960s, students' concerns shifted from social life in fraternities to more political issues of student governance on campus and to broader areas of protest. The Richard L. Cutler series echoes this debate as questions regarding student autonomy and dissent arise in each of the subseries. The Cutler series comprises eighteen inches and consists of four subseries: Administrative, Housing, Student Organization, and Topical. Each subseries is arranged alphabetically and reflects Cutler's organizational scheme. The Administrative and Housing materials reflect students demands for more control over their lives on campus in the files on student participation in University affairs and the dormitory visitation file. Student organizations and topical materials reflect the alienated, activist segment of the student population in the files of Students for a Democratic Society, Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, and Vietnam Protests.
  - Administrative Files, 1950-1969
    - Auditor of Student Organizations, 1953-1968 (Box 7)
    - Committee on Standards and Conduct, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
    - Discipline, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Foreign Students, Coordinating Committee on, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - HUAC Subpoena, Committee on, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
    - Knauss Report (on Student Participation in University Affairs), 1965-1966
      - Background, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
      - Final, 1966 (Box 7)
    - Reed Study Committee (re OSA reorganization), 1962 (Box 7)
    - Reorganization of Office of Student Affairs, 1968 (Box 7)
    - "Role of Student in Decision Making,", 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Rules and Regulations at Other Schools, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Safety Program Recommendations, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Standards for Students, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Student Activities Building Use, 1965-1968 (Box 7)
    - Student Affairs, Committee on, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
    - Student Community Relations (Annual Report), 1965-1966 (Box 7)
    - Tuskegee Exchange Program, 1963-1966 (Box 7)
    - University Activities Center, 1964-1968 (Box 7)
    - Vehicle Permit Office, 1956-1965 (Box 7)
  - Housing, 1963-1969
    - Correspondence, 1965-1968 (Box 7)
    - Dormitories Food Service, 1967-1969 (Box 7)
    - Dormitories Director-Manager Posts, 1965-1966 (Box 7)
    - Fraternities, 1963-1965 (Box 7)
    - Hours and Visitation, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Housing Surveys, 1965
      - Bodkin, Robert, 1965 (Box 7)
      - Gordon, Stewart, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Low Rent, 1968 (Box 7)
    - North Campus, 1967-1969 (Box 7)
    - Off-Campus Housing Summary, 1965-1967 (Box 7)
    - Regents Hearings, 1967-1969
      - Residence Requirements, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
      - Visitation Policy and Women's hours, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - Student Organizations, 1954-1970
    - Cinema Guild, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Graduate Assembly, 1965-1970 (Box 7)
    - Indian Students, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
    - Interfraternity Council, North Campus Development, 1967 (Box 7)
    - Panhellenic Association, 1965-1968 (Box 7)
    - Student Employees Union, 1965 (Box 7)
    - Student Government Council (SGC), 1954-1968
      - Committee on Referral, 1964-1967 (Box 8)
      - Council Plan (Revised), 1968 (Box 8)
      - Financial Survey, 1965 (Box 8)
      - Historical Files, 1954-1965; 4 folders (Box 8)
      - Powers and Responsibilities, 1963-1967 (Box 8)
    - Students for a Democratic Society National Convention, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
    - Student for a Democratic Society-Voice Chapter, 1965-1968 (Box 8)
    - Student Non-Violent Coordinating Committee, 1965 (Box 8)
    - WCBN, 1954-1966 (Box 8)
  - Topical Files, 1952-1969; 1964-1968
    - Apartheid, 1965-1966 (Box 8)
    - Autonomy Issues, 1963-1964 (Box 8)
    - Berkeley Student Movement, 1967 (Box 8)
    - Economic Welfare, 1963-1966 (Box 8)
    - HUAC, 1966 (Box 8)
    - Safety Measures, 1964-1969 (Box 8)
    - Selective Service, 1966-1970 (Box 8)
    - Speaker Policy, 1952-1962 (Box 8)
    - Teach-in, 1965 (Box 8)
    - Viet Nam Protests, 1965-1969 (Box 8)
    - Willow Village-Office of Economic Opportunity Project, 1965 (Box 8)
- Barbara W. Newell, Acting Vice-President for Student Affairs, 1965-1970; 1968-1970
  The Barbara W. Newell series parallels the Cutler series in many respects. Its Administrative, Housing, and Topical subseries constitute eighteen linear inches and are arranged alphabetically within the subseries. The Housing materials were generated by John Feldkamp and evidently consist of that part of Feldkamp's file which ended in the vice-president's records. As with Cutler, Newell's Administrative and Topical files are a rich source with which to examine administration response to student unrest. The bulk of materials in both subseries reflects Newell's attempts to balance the demands of various alienated student protestors with the desires to keep order in the University community. The researcher should note that Newell's organizing format included Student Organizations within the Administrative files.
  - Administrative Files, 1965-1970
    - Advisory Committee on Recreation, Intramurals and Club Sports, Bookstore, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
    - Director's Meetings, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Handicapped Students, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
    - Judiciary, 1967-1969 (Box 8)
    - Michigan Union-Osterheld Report, 1968 (Box 8)
    - 1969-1970 (Box 8)
    - Recruitment and Placement, 1968-1970; 4 folders (Box 9)
      (includes photographs)
    - SACUA, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Student Discipline, 1968-1970
      (see also Judiciary file)
      - Faculty Speeches Regarding Discipline, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
    - Student Government Council, 1965-1968 (Box 9)
    - Student Organizations, 1968-1970
      - Black Student Union, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
      - Fraternities and Sororities, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
      - Michigan Union, 1970 (Box 9)
      - Policy Board, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
      - WCBN, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
    - University Activities Center Blues Festival, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
  - Housing (Partial Run), 1965-1970
    - Audit of Student Residences, 1967-1970 (Box 9)
    - Baits Housing, 1967-1970 (Box 9)
    - Board of Governors, 1968-1970 (Box 9)
    - Coeducational Study Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - Damage Policies, 1966-1970 (Box 9)
    - Fall Housing (Temporary), 1969 (Box 9)
    - Feldkamp, John (Housing Director), 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Finances, 1965-1970 (Box 9)
    - Hours and Visitation Policy, 1967-1968 (Box 9)
    - Housing Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 9)
    - Lawyers Club, 1968-1969 (Box 9)
    - Meal Policies, 1965-1969 (Box 9)
    - Misconduct in Student Housing, 1967-1970 (Box 9)
  - Topical Files, 1968-1970
    - Black Action Movement, 1970 (Box 9)
    - Environmental Teach-in, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Rent Strike, 1969-1970 (Box 9)
    - South University Incident, 1969 (Box 9)
    - Student Disruption and Protest, 1968 (Box 9)
    - University School, Closing of, 1969 (Box 9)
- Robert L. Knauss, Vice-President for Student Services, 1962-1973; 1970-1972
  Beginning with the Robert L. Knauss series, the vice-presidents for Student Services organized their current materials into topical files by academic year. Since Knauss' tenure spanned less than two academic years, this topical file has been compressed into a single run. Even so, the Knauss topical file subseries is fragmentary. The Historical (Subject Reference) subseries is more extensive, comprising ten of the fifteen linear inches of Knauss material. It is also a richer source of material for both the traditional health, housing, and student organization concerns of Student Services and the temporally bound issues of student unrest.
  - Historical (Subject Reference) Files, 1962-1971; 1969-1971 (Box 10)
    - Child Care Center, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
    - Credit Union, Student, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
    - Decision Making, Student Role in, 1966-1971 (Box 10)
    - Firearms, Rules and Regulations on, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Health Service, 1968-1971 (Box 10)
    - Annual Report to the President, 1969-1970 (Box 10)
    - Housing, 1966-1971 (Box 10)
    - Huber Report on Campus Disorders, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
    - Office of Student Services Reorganization, 1970-1971; 3 folders (Box 10)
    - Pilot Program, 1965-1971 (Box 10)
    - Police Relations, 1968-1970 (Box 10)
    - Recreational Facilities, 1966-1968 (Box 10)
    - Religious Affairs, Office of, 1962-1969 (Box 10)
    - Rent Strike, 1968-1969 (Box 10)
    - Student Government Council, 1963-1970 (Box 10)
    - Student Relations Committee, 1967-1970 (Box 10)
    - Surveys (on Student Housing 1969 and Student Concerns, 1969), 1969-1971 (Box 10)
    - Tent City, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Veterans, 1969-1971 (Box 10)
  - Topical Files, 1968-1973; 1970-1972
    - Advisory Committee on Recreation, Intramural and Club Sports, 1967-1972; 2 folders (Box 10)
    - Black Student Activities, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
    - Committee for the Handicapped (photos), 1970-1972 (Box 10)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
    - Discrimination, 1970-1972 (Box 10)
    - Environmental Health and Safety, 1968-1972 (Box 10)
    - Facilities, Use of, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
    - Financial Statements, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Health Service, 1969-1972
      - Policy Committee, Long-Range Planning, 1971 (Box 11)
    - Judicial System, 1972 (Box 11)
    - Office of Special Services and Programs, 1971-1972 (Box 11)
    - Police Protection, 1972 (Box 11)
- Henry Johnson, Vice-President of Student Services, 1950-1985; 1972-1985
  The Henry Johnson series was received in several accessions. The bulk of the files are from Johnson's tenure, but there are files from his predecessors dating back to 1950. The Henry Johnson series is divided into two subseries: Annual Files, 1972/73-1985 and a Topical File covering approximately the same years.
  - Annual Files, 1972-1985
    This Annual Files is arranged by academic year, 1972-1973 to 1984-1985 and thereunder alphabetically. This format closely conforms to the original order of Johnson's materials. The researcher should be aware that the annual files are of uneven depth and breadth. As the annual files tend to contain materials spanning several years, the unevenness of amounts of materials is smoothed. Recurrent themes in Johnson's files include: Housing, Health Services, Counseling, Student Government, Michigan Union, University Activities Center, Career Planning and Placement, Disabled Student Services and Minority Affairs. These last two fields reflect the office's capacity for expansion to provide an enduring institutional framework within which to advance the interests and needs of special categories of students. Johnson's notes on the Executive Officers minutes provide an interesting insight into the dynamics of these meetings.
    - 1972-1973 Annual File, 1967-1973 1972-1973
      - Advisory Committee on Recreational Intramural and Club Sports, 1967-1973 (Box 11)
      - Budget Hearings-Office of Student Services Policy Board, 1972 (Box 11)
      - Coalition for Use of Learning Skills, 1972 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Counseling, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
      - Freedom School, 1972 (Box 11)
      - Living-Learning Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Office of Student Services, Assistant to Vice-President, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Coalition for Use of Learning Skills, 1972 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Counseling, 1970-1972 (Box 11)
      - Freedom School, 1972 (Box 11)
      - Living-Learning Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Minority Recruitment, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Office of Student Services, Assistant to Vice-President, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Regents, 1971-1973 (Box 11)
      - SACUA (Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs), 1971-1973 (Box 11)
    - 1973-1974 Annual File, 1970-1974 1973-1974
      - ACRICS (Advisory Committee on Recreational, Intramural and Club Sports), 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Ann Arbor Community Coalition, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
      - Black Caucus Against Drugs, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Career Planning and Placement, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
      - Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Counseling, 1972-1973 (Box 11)
      - Disabled Student Services, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Management Advisory Group, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
      - Mental Health, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Personal Correspondence, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Religion and Ethics, 1971-1973 (Box 11)
      - "Rights and Responsibilities of University Administrators,", 1972 (Box 11)
      - Student Governance Commission, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Student Government Council, 1972-1974 (Box 11)
      - University Activities Center, 1970-1974 (Box 11)
      - Vice-Presidents Group, 1971-1973 (Box 11)
    - 1974-1975 Annual File, 1967-1975 1974-1975
      - Black Affairs, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Career Planning and Placement, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
      - Counseling, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Disabled Student Services Program, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
      - Health Services, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
      - Human Sexuality, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1971-1974 (Box 12)
      - Minority Enrollment, 1970-1974 (Box 12)
      - Office of Special Services Program, 1972-1974 (Box 12)
      - Personal Correspondence, 1971-1975 (Box 12)
      - Policy Governing Student Records, 1967-1975 (Box 12)
      - Research and Development Committee, 1973-1975; 2 folders (Box 12)
      - Student Fees and Aid, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Student Governance Commission, 1973-1975
        - Drafts and Comments, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
        - Final Report, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
        - Minutes and Memos, 1973-1975 (Box 12)
        - Writers Group, 1974 (Box 12)
      - Student Government Council, 1972-1974 (Box 12)
      - Student Miscellaneous, 1974-1975 (Box 12)
      - Trotter House, 1971-1973 (Box 12)
    - 1975-1976 Annual File, 1966-1976 1975-1976
      - Career Planning and Placement, 1973-1975 (Box 13)
      - Childcare, 1971-1975 (Box 13)
      - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
      - Disabled Student Services, 1974-1976 (Box 13)
      - Executive Officers (Johnson's Notes on Meetings), 1973-1976 (Box 13)
      - Graduate School, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
      - Health Service, 1974-1976 (Box 13)
      - Housing, 1971-1976
        - Complaints, 1971-1976
        - Feldkamp, John (Memos and letters), 1972-1975 (Box 13)
        - Married Student, 1971-1973 (Box 13)
        - Single Student, 1975 (Box 13)
        - Statistics and Reports, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
        - International Center, 1966-1974 (Box 13)
        - Michigan Student Assembly (formerly Student Government Council), 1974-1976 (Box 13)
        - Students (Miscellaneous), 1974-1975 (Box 13)
        - Student fees, 1975 (Box 13)
        - Student Records (Education Amendments Acts of 1974) (Box 13)
        - Student Relations Committee, 1972-1976 (Box 13)
        - University Council, 1972-1975 (Box 13)
        - Washington Intern Program, 1969-1976 (Box 13)
        - Women, 1972-1974 (Box 13)
    - 1976-1977 Annual File, 1950-1977 1976-1977
      - Annual Reports, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
      - Barbour-Waterman Gym, 1950-1977 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
      - National Association of Student Personnel Administrators-Report on Ethnic Minorities, 1977 (Box 14)
      - Office of Student Services Directors, 1975-1977 (Box 14)
      - Personal Correspondence, 1974-1977 (Box 14)
      - WCBN, 1974-1977 (Box 14)
    - 1977-1978 Annual Files, 1970-1978 1977-1978
      - Affirmative Action, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
      - Annual Reports, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
      - Asian Americans, 1974-1976 (Box 14)
      - Black Affairs, 1974-1976 (Box 14)
      - Career Planning and Placement, 1972-1977 (Box 14)
      - Chicano Affairs, 1972-1978 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 14)
      - Counseling, 1974-1977 (Box 14)
      - Disabled Student Services, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
      - Ethics and Religion, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
      - Executive Officers (H. Johnson notes), 1975-1977 (Box 14)
      - Fleming Correspondence, 1972-1977 (Box 14)
      - Housing, 1974-1978
        - Complaints, 1976-1978 (Box 14)
        - General, 1976-1977 (Box 14)
        - Married Students, 1974-1977 (Box 14)
        - Planning and Rates, 1975-1977 (Box 14)
        - Single Student, 1975-1978 (Box 14)
      - Ombudsman [including Freedom of Information], 1976-1977 (Box 14)
      - Project Community, 1971-1977 (Box 14)
      - Religious Affairs, 1970-1977 (Box 14)
      - Research, 1975-1977 (Box 15)
      - Special Services and Programs, 1975-1978 (Box 15)
      - Student Data Systems Task Force, 1975-1977 (Box 15)
      - Student Fees and Information, 1975-1977 (Box 15)
      - Student, Miscellaneous, 1976-1978 (Box 15)
      - Student Organizations, 1972-1976 (Box 15)
      - Student Relations Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 15)
      - University Activities Center, 1974-1977 (Box 15)
      - Use of Facilities, 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - Washington Intern Program, 1975-1978 (Box 15)
      - WCBN, 1975-1978 (Box 15)
    - 1978-1979 Annual file (fragment), 1977-1979 1978-1979
      - Affirmative Action, 1977-1979 (Box 15)
      - Memos, 1978 (Box 15)
      - Personal Correspondence, 1977-1979 (Box 15)
      - WCBN, 1978-1979 (Box 15)
    - 1979-1980 Annual File, 1974-1980 1979-1980
      - Career Planning and Placement, 1979-1980 (Box 15)
      - Executive Officers (Johnson's notes), 1979-1980 (Box 15)
      - Health Services, 1974-1980 (Box 15)
      - Housing, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
      - International Center, 1976-1980 (Box 15)
      - Michigan Student Assembly, 1978-1980 (Box 15)
      - Michigan Union, 1977-1980
        - General, 1977-1980 (Box 15)
        - Report of the Task Force to Study the Future of, 1979 (Box 15)
    - 1979-1980 Annual File, 1974-1980 1979-1980 (cont.)
      - Michigan Vice-Presidents for Student Services, 1976-1980 (Box 16)
      - Minority Enrollment, 1975-1980 (Box 16)
      - Office of Student Services Directors, 1978-1980 (Box 16)
      - Student Fees and Aid, 1977-1979 (Box 16)
    - 1980-1981 Annual File (fragment), 1979-1981 1980-1981
      - Career Planning and Placement, 1979-1980 (Box 16)
      - Executive Officers (Johnson's Notes), 1980-1981 (Box 16)
      - Functional Review (of Office of Student Services), 1980-1981 (Box 16)
      - Health Service, 1980-1981 (Box 16)
    - 1981-1982 Annual File (fragment), 1976-1982 1981-1982
      - Advisory Committee on Recreational, Intramural and Club Sports, 1979-1981 (Box 16)
      - Career Planning re Placement, 1980-1982
      - Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 16)